# FAUSTO ARIEL LORENZO

16 Dix St., Worcester, MA, 01609 | P: 774-329-6395 | ariellorenzo08@gmail.com

## **PROFILE**

IT customer service specialist with knowledge and hands-on experience in all aspects of web development and system administration. Enthusiastic team player and willing to go above and beyond to make sure the work is done efficiently.

			EX			

- ☐ Excellent programming and design skills
- ☐ Strong system administration knowledge
- ☐ Proficient in Python, C#, PHP, SQL, JavaScript, React, Vue, VB.NET, HTML, CSS, AJAX, XML, C, Java
- ☐ Strong collaborative and problem-solving skills
- ☐ ASP.NET MVC and WebForms, Django, Flask, PHP/MySQL
- ☐ Bash, PowerShell

## **EXPERIENCE**

**KP & Sons Automotive** - Customer Support

NOVEMBER 2019 - MARCH 2020

- ☐ Activate and manage the infrastructure of the devices in the office, including networking, computer maintenance
- ☐ Manage and assist in website creation (SVG, Wordpress)
- ☐ Assist in company advertising and graphic design (SVG)

### **Keypoint Intelligence** - Back-End Systems Engineer

JANUARY 2018 - NOVEMBER 2018

- ☐ Built back-end database SQL Server functions and procedures for the company website, bliQ (SQL, SQL Server)
- ☐ Assist in the overall change of the back-end intranet applications (ASP.NET WebForms, C#, VB.NET)
- ☐ Drastically improve runtime and execution of procedures and functions (SQL Server, T-SQL)

#### **SAI Global** - Software Engineer

MAY 2017 - OCTOBER 2017

- ☐ Built and deployed a large amount of web courses (HTML5, JavaScript, XML)
- ☐ Repaired and made recommendations on courses built either by me or other employees (HTML5, JavaScript, XML)

#### Information Systems, Southern Adventist University - Software Engineer

MAY 2016 - JANUARY 2017

- ☐ Recreated the back-end functionality for the university account login site still used today (ASP.NET MVC, C#,, HTML5,CSS,JavaScript, jQuery)
- ☐ Design front-end view of main site search for students that is still used today (ASP.NET MVC, C#, Bootstrap, HTML5,CSS,JavaScript, jQuery)
- ☐ Assist in project planning and fix current projects (ASP.NET MVC, C#, Angular, HTML5, CSS, JavaScript, ¡Query)

# School of Education & Psychology, Southern Adventist University - Computer Lab Manager SEPTEMBER 2015 - AUGUST 2016

SEPTEIVIDER 2013 - AUGUST 2010

- ☐ Assessed customer needs and made recommendations
- ☐ Implemented agreed upon solutions and employee rotation schedule
- ☐ Changed the look and content of the department site (HTML, CSS)

### Online Campus, Southern Adventist University - Web Programming Specialist

MAY 2015 - JANUARY 2016

- ☐ Created back-end functionality for the university web tools online directory still used today (PHP/MySQL, C#, .NET)
- ☐ Made recommendations on web software for online classes that are still used today (PHP/MySQL)

### **EDUCATION**

**Southern Adventist University, Collegedale, TN** - B.S. Computer Systems Administration JULY 2011 - DECEMBER 2016

☐ Coursework in networking, programming, software development, computer architectures, databases, server administration, and virtualization